Mas **Anwar Sadat**

Summary

HR Professional with more than 10 years of work experience in managing the recruitment, compensation & benefit, talent development & performance management within various industry such as Hospitality Industry (Hotels & F&B sector), Oil & Gas and Business Consultancy is a business partner who has strong leadership with outstanding interpersonal relation skills and keen sense of responsibility.

Typical of adaptive person, energetic, enthusiastic, dynamic and a good listener. Enjoy being part of in managing, motivating, developing an individual person. Discipline in managing and operating the task on timely manner.

Areas of Expertise

Recruitment & Selection (process, planning, budgeting & manning.)

Designing recruitment strategy with cost efficient and promote diversity at workplace. Managing recruitment from management to line member level

- Compensation & Benefit

Including Payroll, Final settlement/End of Service benefit. Designing benefit & grading wise and salary range for each position based on the market survey & Prepare budget for new opening businesses

- Learning and Development

Designing monthly training calendar according to business and operation needs

- Talent & Performance Management and Retention

Designing appreciation award, retention, bonus plan, career succession plan and performance review annually including company's policy & procedures.

- Employee Relations & People Management

Handling Grievances & Disciplinary Action including conduct internal investigation, provide coaching and counselling.

Reports and Administration

Prepare and produce monthly turn over report including sickness, absenteeism report, training completion report, payroll cost, hiring cost, separation cost.

Professional Experience

Group HR Manager - April 2022 to Present Coastal Investment Group and & Coastal Hospitality. Dubai UAE.

HR Manager - March 2021 to March 2022

AKKA Technologies Middle East DMCC. Dubai, UAE.

 Managing all the HR aspects and operational duties from on boarding to Off boarding including recruitment and people management for UAE, Qatar & Singapore region

Assistant People & Culture Manager - April 2020 to March 2021

Renaissance Downtown Hotel (franchise by Marriott) and EHG. Dubai, UAE

Responsible for recruitment, compensation & benefit, and people management.

HR Executive – January 2019 to April 2020 Conrad Hotel by Hilton. Dubai, UAE

Cluster HR Executive – April 2016 to January 2019 Accor Hotels, Novotel, Adagio and Ibis Al Barsha

Regional HR Executive – June 2014 to March 2016 PT Indonesia Media Television. Surabaya, Indonesia

Recruitment Officer – September 2013 to May 2014 Doha Petroleum Construction Ltd. Doha, Qatar

Regional HR Supervisor – January 2012 – September 2013 Retaj Hotels & Hospitality. Doha, Qatar

Internship – Management Trainee – February 2009 to February 2010 Shangri-la Barr Al Jissah Resport & Spa, Muscat, Oman



Personal Details

00971 (0) 501357581 masanwars@gmail.com

Indonesian National

Education

Holds Higher Diploma Degree in Hotel & Tourism Management

Certifications & Trainings

- Behavioural Based Interview
- Dedicated to Excellent
- HEARTIST of the month
- TWI Training Program
- IMA QATAR Foundation -Quality of Management System (ISO 9001:2008)
- AHLEI American Hotel & Lodging Educational Institute
- Customer Delight Program Award by Shangri-La Hotel Oman